Guide to the Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 23 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 23 records
1936-2015
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
6202
6202-001
Office and Professional Employees International Union.$bLocal 23 (Tacoma, Wash.)
10.62 cubic feet 10 boxes and 1 oversize vertical file
Materials related to the Office and Professional Employees Inernational Union Local 23, Tacoma, Washington
Office and Professional Employees Local 23 represented workers in the Tacoma area until the organization merged into OPEIU Local 8 of Seattle in 2015.
Arranged in 6 series.
Series 1, Meeting Minutes and Financial Statements, 1937-2002
Series 2, Discontinued CBA files and Miscellaneous papers, 1936-1997
Series 3, Organizing Campaigns and miscellaneous, 1954-1994
Series 4, Former Employer (Retail Store A-U) CBAs & Correspondence, 1937-2007
Series5, Newsletters, 1956-2015
Series 6, Miscellaneous, photographs and newspaper clippings, 1936-2009
Records of the Tacoma local of the Office and Professional Employees International Union, including files on organizing campaigns, collective bargaining files and correspondence with employers; meeting minutes, newsletters, photographs & press clippings. Meeting minutes also include minutes from the Office Workers Local 20360 and OPEIU Local 132.
Forms part of the Labor Archives of Washington.
No restrictions on access. Records stored offsite; advance notice is required.
Donated by Libby Alejandro and Cindy Shu of OPEIU Local 8. Local 23 merged into Local 8 in June of 2018.
Office and Professional Employees Local 23 web archive
Office and Professional Employees International Union.$bLocal 23 (Tacoma, Wash.)$vArchives; Office and Professional Employees International Union$xHistory$vSources; White collar workers$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Labor unions$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Labor$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Labor movement$zWashington (State)$xHistory$vSources; Business correspondence; Minutes (Records); Newsletters; Collective labor agreements; Records (Documents); Photographs; Ephemera; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor Unions; Tacoma; Labor History
- Meeting Minutes and Financial Statements, 1937-2002; Series 1
  - Office Workers Union Local 20360, Reports of Secretary Treasurer George P. Firth, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Office Workers Union Local 20360 Constitution and By-Laws; Resume of Union History, Minutes of Regular Meetings, 1936-1943 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Office Workers Union Local 20360 & Office Employees International Union Local 23 Minutes of Regular Meetings, January 1944-December 1947 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Office Employees International Union Local 23 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1944-1948 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Office Employees International Union Local 23 Minutes of the Recording Secretary, 1944-1953 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Office Employees International Union Local 23 Minutes of Regular Meetings and Executive Board Meetings, January 1944-December 1947 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Trial Board Transcript of Proceedings Re Walter Huntsman, February 27, 1948 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Office Employees International Union Local 23 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, Partial 1948, 1948-1965 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Office Employees International Union Local 23 Minutes of Regular Meetings and Executive Board Meetings, January 1948-December 1960 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - OPEIU Local 132 Bremerton Meeting Minutes (Merged with OPEIU Local 23 1969), October 1957, 1969 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - OPEIU Local 23 General Membershi Meeting Minutes, January 1975-November 2002 (Box-folder 1/11-1/15)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, January 1981-October 2002 (Box-folder 1/16-2/2)
  - OEIU Constitutional Convention Amendments, 1949-1955 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - OPEIU International Convention, 2004-2010 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Model Constitution and By-Laws, 2007 (Box-folder 2/5)
- Discontinued CBA files and Miscellaneous papers, 1936-1997; Series 2
  - Kitsap County Commissioners, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - B&I Sales, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 2/7)
  - Precision Machine Works, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Port of Tacoma, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Hotels-Lincolnshire, Olympius and Tacoma, 1937-1950 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Winthrop Hotel, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Fisher's/ Bon Marche, 1957-1978 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Nalley's, 1942-1972 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Weber Plumbing, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Tacoma Transit Company, 1937-1946 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - J.C. Penny, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 2/16)
  - J.C. Penny, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 2/17)
  - Retail Stores Negotiations, 1944-1948 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Local 20360 Charter, misc. papers, 1936 (Box-folder 2/19)
  - Organizing Campaigns, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 2/20)
  - OPEIU Local 11 Merger Exploration, 1978 (Box-folder 2/21)
  - Washington State Office Worker minimum wage hearing, 1941 (Box-folder 2/22)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Wage surveys, 1940-1962, 1972 (Box-folder 2/23)
  - Union Bank, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 2/24)
  - Samaritan Hospital Organzing Committee Brochure, undated (Box-folder 2/25)
  - Budget and Finance committee, 1943-1949 (Box-folder 2/26)
  - Elections, 1944-1949 (Box-folder 2/27)
  - Constitution and By-Laws Correspondence with international, 1948-1979 (Box-folder 2/28-2/29)
  - Mary Kresevich Hegland case, 1951 (Box-folder 2/30)
  - W.L. Huntsman case, 1948 (Box-folder 2/31)
  - Kerschner, Floyd S. case, 1974 (Box-folder 2/32)
  - McIntyre case, 1949 (Box-folder 2/33)
  - C.H. Atteberry wage claim, 1948 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Retail Stores Shop Stewards Committee, 1961 (Box-folder 2/35)
  - Tacoma Retail Stores strike, 1948 (Box-folder 2/36)
  - War efforts, 1945 (Box-folder 2/37)
  - Initiative 198, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 2/38)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1978 (Box-folder 2/39)
  - Tacoma Mini committee, 1983 (Box-folder 2/40)
  - Blood Bank membership drive, 1952-1982 (Box-folder 2/41)
  - Peoples Department Store, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 2/42)
  - Foreman & Clark, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 2/43)
  - Sears, 1956-1966 (Box-folder 2/44)
  - Community Bank of Renton, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 2/45)
  - Bridge Clinic, 1942 (Box-folder 2/46)
  - Kitsap Federal Credit Union, Negotiations, 1987 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - United Way of Kitsap County, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - Kitsap Physicians Service, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Washington Natural Gas Company, 1994 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Washington Natural Gas Company, 1948-1992 (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Washington Natural Gas Company, 1995 (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Washington Natural Gas Company, 1996 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Washington Natural Gas Company, 1997 (Box-folder 3/8)
  - Hunt Foods, Inc., 1950-1956 (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Graham Blue Print, 1948-1958 (Box-folder 3/10)
  - Credit Bureau of Tacoma, 1955-1968 (Box-folder 3/11)
  - J. Hoffert Co, 1970-1982 (Box-folder 3/12)
  - Western clinic, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 3/13)
  - Trade Union Offices, misc papers, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 3/14)
  - Misc. Discountinued CBAs, 1948-1981 (Box-folder 3/15)
  - Seattle Retail Store employees, 1972 (Box-folder 3/16)
  - Andrews Letter Shop, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 3/17)
  - Attorney Offices, 1961-1974 (Box-folder 3/18)
  - Auto Clearing House, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 3/19)
  - B-B's Washer Service and Appliances, 1954-1959 (Box-folder 3/20)
  - B&I Sales Co., 1955-1958 (Box-folder 3/21)
  - Boyle and Eller, Attorneys, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 3/22)
  - Bridge Clinic, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 3/23)
  - Broadway Furniture, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 3/24)
  - C and Electric Co., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 3/25)
  - Community Bank of Renton, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3/26)
  - Consolidated Freightways, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 3/27)
  - Cowlitz Medical Service (King County Blue Shield), 1983-1995 (Box-folder 3/28)
  - Cowlitz Medical Service (King County Blue Shield), 1982-1988 (Box-folder 3/29)
  - Cowlitz Medical Service (King County Blue Shield), 1989-1995 (Box-folder 3/30)
  - Craig Furniture, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 3/31)
  - Credit Bureau of Tacoma, 1955-1969 (Box-folder 3/32)
  - Dairies, 1955-1960 (Box-folder 4/1)
  - Graham Blue Print, 1942-1959 (Box-folder 4/2)
  - Griffin & Enslow, Attorneys, 1971 (Box-folder 4/3)
  - Harmon Mfg. Co., 1960 (Box-folder 4/4)
  - J. Hofert Co., 1960 (Box-folder 4/5)
  - Home Electric Co., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - Home Furniture Co., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/7)
  - Hopper-Kelley Co., 1946-1947 (Box-folder 4/8)
  - Hotels, 1937-1957 (Box-folder 4/9)
  - Hunt Foods, 1950-1956 (Box-folder 4/10)
  - Interstate Freight Lines, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 4/11)
  - Lakewood Pacific Ambulance, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 4/12)
  - Lent's Inc., 1975-1982 (Box-folder 4/13-4/14)
  - Nalley's, Signed Agreements, 1942-1959 (Box-folder 4/15)
  - Nalley's, Correspondence/Negotiations, 1946-1949, 1959 (Box-folder 4/16)
  - Nalley's Correspondence, 1959-1932 (Box-folder 4/17)
  - Nalley's organizing, 1972 (Box-folder 4/18)
  - Old Tacoma Electric Company, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 4/19)
  - Otto's North End Electric Shop, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 4/20)
  - Overland Furniture & Investment Co., 1946-1950 (Box-folder 4/21)
  - Plumbing & Heating Service, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box-folder 4/22)
  - Port of Tacoma, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 4/23)
  - Percision Machine Works, 1957-1969 (Box-folder 4/24)
  - C.J. Rockey Co., 1968-1969 (Box-folder 4/25)
  - Sepic Electric Co., 1946-1948 (Box-folder 4/26)
  - Seymour's Store, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 4/27)
  - Tacoma Railway & Power Co., 1937-1949 (Box-folder 4/28)
  - Thurston County Medical Bureau, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 4/29)
  - United Way of Kitsap County, correspondence/negotiations, 1958-1989 (Box-folder 4/30)
  - United Way of Kitsap County, correspondence, 1958-1997 (Box-folder 4/31)
  - WA Coop Egg & Poultry Assoc., Unsigned agreements/correspondence, 1937-1946 (Box-folder 4/32)
  - WA Steel Products, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 4/33)
  - Weber Plumbing, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 4/34)
  - Western Clinic, signed agreements/correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 4/35)
  - Western Clinic, organizing and unsigned agreement, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 4/36)
  - Wible Radio Supply, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 4/37)
  - Winthrop Hotel, correspondence/negotiations, 1946-1964 (Box-folder 5/1)
  - Winthrop Hotel, signed agreements, 1940-1963 (Box-folder 5/2)
  - YWCA, signed agreements, 1942-1982 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - Office Employees News, Tacoma, October 1945-November 1945 (Box-folder 5/4)
  - Pierce County Labor: To Live in Dignity, 1989 (Box-folder 5/5)
  - Retail Stores Strike, 1948-1965 (Box-folder 5/6)
  - Bon Marche Strike, 1958 (Box-folder 5/7)
  - Washintgon State Labor Council, 1977, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 5/8)
  - Sears-Bellingham OEIU Local 134 Correspondence, 1955 (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Tacoma Labor Advocate, 1972, 1976 (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Grays Harbor CLC Affiliation, 1963 (Box-folder 5/11)
  - War Labor Board Panel, Case No. 111-3496-D Tacoma Offices Bldgs. & Bldg. Service Employees Int't Union Local 38, 1943 (Box-folder 5/12)
  - Pacific Coast Shipbuilding Conference, 1945 (Box-folder 5/13)
  - Pacific Advance Base Depot, 1945 (Box-folder 5/14)
  - Seattle Tacoma Shipbuilding Corporation, 1939-1951 (Box-folder 5/15)
  - American Smelting & Refining, signed agreements, 1948-1967 (Box-folder 5/16)
  - American Smelting & Refining, Grievances and negotiations, 1957-1967 (Box-folder 5/17)
  - American Smelting & Refining,Arbitrations and Correspondence, 1946-1956 (Box-folder 5/18)
  - Associated Retailers, Signed Agreements, 1948-1978 (Box-folder 5/19)
  - Conference of Northwest OEIU Locals, 1947-1949, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 5/20)
  - Donations, 1945-1984 (Box-folder 5/21)
  - Office Emloyes International Union, 1944-1948 (Box-folder 5/22)
  - Screen Office Employees Guild, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5/23)
  - Pamphlets, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 5/24)
  - Bon Marche, Contracts/neogtiations/grievances, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 5/25)
  - Financial Statements, 1947-1975 (Box-folder 5/26)
  - Know Your Union, 1970-1991 (Box-folder 5/27)
  - Retail Stores agreement, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 5/28)
- Organizing Campaigns and miscellaneous, 1954-1994; Series 3
  - AVRE Plasma Center, Certification of election results, 1985 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - Centralia Convalescent Center, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 6/2)
  - Clover Park School District, 1973 (Box-folder 6/3)
  - Comprehensive Metal Health Center, 1986 (Box-folder 6/4)
  - Day's, Inc., 1954, 1974 (Box-folder 6/5)
  - Ebasco Services Inc. NLRB Case No. 19-RC-9410 Petitioners Brief, 1979 (Box-folder 6/6)
  - Ebasco Services Inc. NLRB Case No. 19-RC-9410 Hrng. Transcript Pt. 1, 1979 (Box-folder 6/7)
  - Ebasco Services Inc. NLRB Case No. 19-RC-9410 Hrng. Transcript Pt. 2, 1979 (Box-folder 6/8)
  - Ebasco Services Inc. General Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 6/9)
  - Ebasco Services Inc. Union Correspondence to Employees, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 6/10)
  - Ebasco Services Inc. Objections to Election, 1981 (Box-folder 6/11)
  - Ebasco Services Inc. General Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 6/12)
  - Federal Collectors, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 6/13)
  - Forks State Bank, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 6/14)
  - Grays Harbor Juvenile Department, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 6/15)
  - Gray's Harbor County Medical Bureau, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 6/16)
  - Hahn Co. (Capital Mall, 1993 (Box-folder 6/17)
  - Hollyridge, 1994 (Box-folder 6/18)
  - Lakewood General Hospital, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 6/19)
  - Monitor Cabinets, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 6/20)
  - Pacific National Bank of Washington, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 6/21)
  - Pacific National Bank of Washingotn, Tacoma EIS Center, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 6/22)
  - Nationwide Cablevision, Corespondence, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 6/23)
- Former Employer (Retail Store A-U) CBAs & Correspondence, 1937-2007; Series 4
  - Associated Retailers of Tacoma, Correspondence, 1953-1970 (Box-folder 6/24)
  - Associated Retailers of Tacoma, Negotiations and Grievances, 1948-1961 (Box-folder 6/25)
  - Bon Marche, Agreements, 1953-1987 (Box-folder 6/26)
  - Bon Marche, Negotiations/ Grievances, 1964-1978 (Box-folder 7/1)
  - Retail Stores, Negotiations, 1937-1947 (Box-folder 7/2)
  - Retail Stores, Signed Agreements, 1944-1963 (Box-folder 7/3)
  - Retail Stores, Negotiations, 1944-1963 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - J.C. Penney (Tacoma Mall), 1965-1975 (Box-folder 7/5)
  - J.C. Penney Decertification, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 7/6)
  - J.C. Penney, Strike, 1975 (Box-folder 7/7)
  - J.C. Penney, Strike, Signed Agreements, 1948, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 7/8)
  - People Store, 1971-1981 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - Rhodes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 7/10)
  - Schoenfelds, 1969-1981 (Box-folder 7/11)
  - Schoenfelds agreements, 1969-1981 (Box-folder 7/12)
  - Sears, Roebuck & Co., Agreements, 1953-1966 (Box-folder 7/13)
  - Sears, Roebuck & Co., Correspondence, 1952-1966 (Box-folder 7/14)
  - Selden's, Inc., 1946-1969 (Box-folder 7/15)
  - Weisfield, Goldberg, Inc., Agreements, 1946-1969 (Box-folder 7/16)
  - Weisfield, Goldberg, Inc., Correspondence, 1947-1966 (Box-folder 7/17)
  - Woolworth, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 7/18)
  - Foreman and Clark, 1958-1972 (Box-folder 7/19)
  - Helen Davis Apparel Shop, 1946-1952 (Box-folder 7/20)
  - Irving's Clothes Shop, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 7/21)
  - Knettle's Corsetry, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 7/22)
  - Lerner Shops, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 7/23)
  - S.H. Kress & Company, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 7/24)
  - Lundquist-Lilly Men's Wear, 1946-1953 (Box-folder 7/25)
  - Lyons Apparel, 1952-1971 (Box-folder 7/26)
  - Nordstrom, 1966-1979 (Box-folder 7/27)
  - Norman's Apparel Shop, 1946-1953 (Box-folder 7/28)
  - Tacoma Grocery Co., 1938-1955 (Box-folder 7/29)
  - Valu-Mart, 1960-1975 (Box-folder 7/30)
  - White Front, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 7/31)
  - Kitsap Administrative Services, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 7/32)
  - KitsapCounty CLC, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 7/33)
  - Kitsap Federal Credit Union, Arbitration, 1987 (Box-folder 7/34)
  - Kitsap Federal Credit Union, 1960-1988 (Box-folder 7/35)
  - Kitsap Physicians Service, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 7/36)
  - Kitsap Physicians Service, 1985-2001 (Box-folder 7/37)
  - Kitsap Physicians Service, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 7/38)
  - Kitsap Physicians Service, 1961-1977 (Box-folder 7/39)
  - Labor Advocate, 1959-1978 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Laborers Local 486, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Laundry Workers Local 42, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 8/3)
  - McDaniel & Hallstrom, CPAs, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Millmens Local 1689, 1977-1992 (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Olympic Peninsula Bldg. & Construction Trades Council, 1959-2007 (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Painters Local 64, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 8/7)
  - Pierce County Bldg. & Contrcution Trades Council, 1963-1983 (Box-folder 8/8)
  - Pierce County Fire District #2 Terminiation, 2005 (Box-folder 8/9)
  - Pierce County Fire District #2, 1998-2005 (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Pierce County Fire District #3, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 8/11)
  - Pierce County HERE Trust Fund, 1971-1987 (Box-folder 8/12)
  - Pierce County Medical Bureau, agreements, 1955-1980 (Box-folder 8/13)
  - Pierce County Medical Bureau, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 8/14)
  - SEIU Local 123, 1963-1996 (Box-folder 8/15)
  - SEIU Local 262, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 8/16)
  - Sheet Metal Workers Local 99, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Sheet Metal Workers Local 150, 1963-1988 (Box-folder 8/18)
  - Tacoma Radiology Associates, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - UFCW Local 381 Bremerton (Retail Clerks) Signed agreements, 1972-2005 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - UFCW Local 553, 1967-1983 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - UFCW Local 554, 1968-1994 (Box-folder 8/22)
  - Union Bank, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 8/23)
- Newsletters, 1956-2015; Series5
  - OPEIU Local 23 Newsletters, 1956-1974 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Newsletters, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Newsletters, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Newsletters, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Newsletters, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Newsletters, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Newsletters, 1992-2002 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Newsletters, 2003-2015 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Newsletters, 1993-2003 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Newsletters, 1960-1992 (Box-folder 9/10)
- Miscellaneous, photographs and newspaper clippings, 1936-2009; Series 6
  - Miscellaneous old agreements, 1946-2011 (Box-folder 8/24)
  - Manuals and regualtions, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 8/25)
  - Notes and letters, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 8/26)
  - Certificates, 1982 (Box-folder 8/27)
  - Flyers, undated (Box-folder 8/28)
  - OPEIU Photographs, 1980-2009 (Box-folder 8/29)
  - Photographs, 1980-1990s (Box-folder 8/30)
  - Photographs, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 8/31)
  - Photographs, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 8/32)
  - Photographs, 2000-2010 (Box-folder 8/33)
  - Photographs (Box-folder 8/34)
  - OPEIU Local 23 History & Special Articles, 1986-1990s (Box-folder 9/11)
  - OPEIU Local 23 Duplicate newsletters, 1948-1992 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1938-2005 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Historical pictures, newspaper clippings, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - OPEIU Local 23 History Notes, 1937-2004 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Bank Employees, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1935-1957 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Membership, 1937-1945 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Newspaper articles, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 9/20)
  - Photographs, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Photographs, 1991 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Photographs, 2000-2010 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Photographs, 1981 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Photographs, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Photographs, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Photographs, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Photographs, 1970 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Photographs, 1991, 1986 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Group photo, 1960s (Vf:oversize OSVF 177)